Unbury the past, unleash the nightmare.
The Dogs is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Valerie Buhagiar.
After fleeing his psychotic father, a young teen and his mom seek refuge in a remote farmhouse, only
to face a pack of ferocious dogs and the sinister spirits that haunt the property.
Cameron Weaver, played by Donovan Colan.
Art Sinclair, played by Stuart Hughes.
Dogs (Spanish: Perros) is a 2025 black comedy film written and
directed by Gerardo Minutti in his directorial debut.
It stars Néstor Guzzini, Marcelo Subiotto and María Elena Pérez.
It follows the conflict between two families from different social
classes after the wealthier family's dog disappears.
A co-production between Uruguay and Argentina, the film had its world premiere at the 28th Málaga Film Festival on March 18, 2025, where it competed for
the Golden Biznaga for Best Latin-American Film and María Elena Pérez was honored with the Silver Biznaga for Best Supporting Actress.
The film explores themes of dog, vengeful ghost, haunted by the past.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.